[
	{
		"question": "Imagination",
		"answers": ["Imagination"]
	},
  {
		"question": "representative",
		"answers": ["representative"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Black Sheep",
		"answers": ["Black Sheep"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Boronavirus",
		"answers": ["Boronavirus"]
	},
  {
		"question": "lenny",
		"answers": ["lenny"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Black Sheep is best",
		"answers": ["Black Sheep is best"]
	},
  {
		"question": "digress",
		"answers": ["digress"]
	},
   {
		"question": "gravity",
		"answers": ["gravity"]
	},
  {
		"question": "embarrassment",
		"answers": ["embarrassment"]
	},
  {
		"question": "swell",
		"answers": ["swell"]
	},
  {
		"question": "limited",
		"answers": ["limited"]
	},
  {
		"question": "escape",
		"answers": ["escape"]
	},
  {
		"question": "struggle",
		"answers": ["struggle"]
	},
  {
		"question": "trouble",
		"answers": ["trouble"]
	},
  {
		"question": "predator",
		"answers": ["predator"]
	},
  {
		"question": "oppose",
		"answers": ["oppose"]
	},
  {
		"question": "double",
		"answers": ["double"]
	},
  {
		"question": "spontaneous",
		"answers": ["spontaneous"]
	},
  {
		"question": "drag",
		"answers": ["drag"]
	},
  {
		"question": "retirement",
		"answers": ["retirement"]
	},
	{
		"question": "boomer",
		"answers": ["boomer"]
	}
]